So let's make sure to destroy everything
Hãy chắc chắn chúng ta xóa sạch mọi thứ
before we're done.
trước khi kết thúc.
So first, we need to stop the service.
Đầu tiên, cần dừng service.
So to stop the service,
Để dừng service,
make sure you have zero tasks running.
hãy bảo đảm không còn task nào chạy.
If not, you update the service
Nếu còn, bạn cập nhật service
and you set the desired task to zero.
và đặt desired task về 0.
And then you can click on Delete Service, type in Delete,
Sau đó nhấn Delete Service, gõ Delete,
and this will delete the service.
và service sẽ bị xóa.
Now, when you delete the service,
Khi bạn xóa service,
this is actually going to go
việc này sẽ chuyển sang
into a service called CloudFormation.
một dịch vụ tên CloudFormation.
And CloudFormation is going to take its time
CloudFormation sẽ mất thời gian
to delete the entire stack that it created.
để xóa toàn bộ stack đã tạo.
And so part of the thing it's going to delete
Một phần những gì sẽ xóa
is the ECS service, but also you LoadBalancer Listener,
là ECS service, cả Load Balancer Listener,
you LoadBalancer itself, the security group,
Load Balancer, security group,
and the target groups.
và các target group.
So this can take a little bit of time
Việc này sẽ mất một chút thời gian
and we need to wait for everything to be deleted.
và ta phải chờ mọi thứ bị xóa.
And when the service is fully deleted,
Khi service xóa xong,
then you can go and delete this cluster.
bạn có thể xóa cluster.
So for this, you just click on Delete Cluster
Chỉ cần nhấn Delete Cluster
and it's going to delete the demo cluster.
để xóa demo cluster.
And we can do this right now.
Ta có thể làm ngay bây giờ.
And again, this is going to start something
Một lần nữa, việc này sẽ kích hoạt
in CloudFormation to delete the infrastructure
trong CloudFormation để xóa hạ tầng
of the ECS cluster.
của ECS cluster.
So that includes the capacity provider,
Bao gồm cả capacity provider,
the auto-scaling group that we have created,
auto scaling group chúng ta tạo,
the cluster, and the launch templates.
cluster và launch template.
So this is very good.
Vậy là ổn.
Finally, for your task definition, you can leave them as is.
Cuối cùng, bạn có thể giữ nguyên task definition.
They don't cost you any money, they're just definitions.
Chúng không tốn phí, chỉ là định nghĩa.
But if you wanted to,
Nhưng nếu muốn,
you could also click on one of them and deregister.
bạn có thể chọn một cái và deregister.
Do Action and deregister the test definition itself.
Chọn Action và deregister task definition.
So that's it.
Vậy là xong.
I hope you liked it and I will see you in the next lecture.
Hy vọng bạn thích, hẹn gặp ở bài tiếp theo.